<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Story on 小宋小宋?</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/story/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Story on 小宋小宋?</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This is a customized copyright.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of&#xA;this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on&#xA;by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to&#xA;listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined&#xA;to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on&#xA;the part of the public. This gleam of hope acquired fresh life, when he&#xA;saw Quasimodo, Coppenole, and the deafening escort of the pope of the&#xA;procession of fools quit the hall amid great uproar. The throng rushed&#xA;eagerly after them. “Good,” he said to himself, “there go all the&#xA;mischief-makers.” Unfortunately, all the mischief-makers constituted the&#xA;entire audience. In the twinkling of an eye, the grand hall was empty.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago&#xA;to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple&#xA;circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has&#xA;preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus&#xA;set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.&#xA;It was neither an assault by the Picards nor the Burgundians, nor a hunt&#xA;led along in procession, nor a revolt of scholars in the town of Laas, nor&#xA;an entry of “our much dread lord, monsieur the king,” nor even a pretty&#xA;hanging of male and female thieves by the courts of Paris. Neither was it&#xA;the arrival, so frequent in the fifteenth century, of some plumed and&#xA;bedizened embassy. It was barely two days since the last cavalcade of that&#xA;nature, that of the Flemish ambassadors charged with concluding the&#xA;marriage between the dauphin and Marguerite of Flanders, had made its&#xA;entry into Paris, to the great annoyance of M. le Cardinal de Bourbon,&#xA;who, for the sake of pleasing the king, had been obliged to assume an&#xA;amiable mien towards this whole rustic rabble of Flemish burgomasters, and&#xA;to regale them at his Hôtel de Bourbon, with a very “pretty morality,&#xA;allegorical satire, and farce,” while a driving rain drenched the&#xA;magnificent tapestries at his door.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
